<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">
    <string name="app_name">ScoreProf</string>
    <string name="setup">Setup</string>
    <string name="leagues">Leagues</string>
    <string name="league">League</string>
    <string name="league_name">League Name</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="competitions">Competitions</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="email">Email Address</string>
    <string name="create_new_league">Create New League</string>
    <string name="invite_others">Invite Others</string>
    <string name="competition_screen_text">For each match click on the team you predict to win. Click on both teams to predict a draw.</string>
    <string name="home_text_1">Welcome to ScoreProf.</string>
    <string name="home_text_2">You can predict the winners for each match in a multitude of competitions of your choosing.</string>
    <string name="home_text_3">Points are gained per match correctly predicted.</string>
    <string name="home_text_4">Create your own league in Setup. Invite your friends to make their predictions too.</string>
    <string name="home_text_5">Best of luck!</string>
    <string name="create_league">Create League</string>
    <string name="invite_others_by_email">Invite others by email</string>
    <string name="rules">Rules</string>
    <string name="contact">Ideas &amp; Bugs</string>
    <string name="setup_text_1">Select the competitions you would like to see on your home screen.\n</string>
    <string name="setup_text_2">Create your own leagues and invite friends to join you.</string>
    <string name="preferred_language">Preferred language</string>
    <string name="language_screen_text">Select the language you would like to use in the app.</string>
    <string name="edit_league">Edit League</string>
    <string name="matches">Matches</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="category">Category</string>
    <string name="selection">Selection</string>
    <string name="summary">Summary</string>
    <string name="subject">Subject</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="feedback_toast">Feedback sent! Thank you.</string>
    <string name="feedback_button">Send Feedback</string>
    <string name="idea">Idea</string>
    <string name="bug">Bug</string>
    <string name="question">Question</string>
    <string name="other">Other</string>
    <string name="scoreprof_login">ScoreProf Login</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="login_text">Note: If this is your first time logging in, the password you enter will be saved as your permanent password.</string>
    <string name="help_question1">How do I start?</string>
    <string name="help_answer1">Go to Setup, give yourself an in-game name, then select which competitions and leagues you want to be able to see.</string>
    <string name="help_question2">How do I make a prediction?</string>
    <string name="help_answer2">Go to the Matches screen and choose the competition matches you would like to predict. Once the matches page has opened, click on which team you think will win. If you think the match will be a draw, click on both team names. Selected teams should be highlighted in green.</string>
    <string name="help_question3">How do I undo a prediction?</string>
    <string name="help_answer3">Go to the Matches page of your prediction and click on the team selected green. It will unselect your prediction.</string>
    <string name="help_question4">How do I earn points?</string>
    <string name="help_answer4">You earn 1 point for every correct result (Home Win, Draw, or Away Win). The result is taken after the match is completed. For example, if the match goes to extra time and a shoot off, the result will be taken after those are complete. For knockout games it is no use choosing a draw.</string>
    <string name="help_question5">When can I make predictions?</string>
    <string name="help_answer5">You can make or change predictions any time up until one minute before the match kicks off.</string>
    <string name="help_question6">Can I see my results?</string>
    <string name="help_answer6">Whilst Match pages will open on the next available match, you can scroll up to see results. If your selected team remains green, your prediction was good. If not, the selection will turn red.</string>
    <string name="help_question7">How do I join a friend\'s league?</string>
    <string name="help_answer7">If your friend has sent you an invite, you can go to \'Setup\' > \'Leagues\', then select the league by checking the checkbox. Once you return to the home screen, you can then select the Leagues option to see your friends league with you now in it.</string>
    <string name="help_question8">How do I change the language displayed?</string>
    <string name="help_answer8">The application will default to the language defined on your phone, if it is available within the application. If you have recently changed the language settings on your phone and the language displayed in the application is not correct, go into the Setup screen and then return to the Home page. This will reinitialise the language displayed. If the application still doesn\'t display in your language, please log a ticket in the \'Ideas &amp; Bugs\' page and we will review for a future release.</string>
    <string name="help_question9">How do I create a league?</string>
    <string name="help_answer9">Go to \'Setup\' > \'Leagues\' and click the \'+\' button at the bottom of the list of leagues. You must give the league a name and select a single competition. You can then invite friends by inserting their emails into the email text field at the bottom of the page, and click \'Add\' to confirm the email is correct. Once you have added your friends\' emails, click on the Save button to create the league. You will be returned to the Setup Leagues screen. Ensure your new league is selected for you to see it in the application.</string>
    <string name="help_question10">How do I edit a league?</string>
    <string name="help_answer10">Go to \'Setup\' > \'Leagues\' and click the triple dot icon to the right of the league you wish to edit. Then choose \'Edit League\'. Remember to save your league once the edit is complete. Note, you can only edit leagues which you have created.</string>
    <string name="help_question11">How do I delete a league?</string>
    <string name="help_answer11">Go to \'Setup\' > \'Leagues\' and click the triple dot icon to the right of the league you wish to delete. Note, you can only delete leagues which you have created.</string>
    <string name="help_question12">How do I report an issue or an idea?</string>
    <string name="help_answer12">Go to \'Ideas &amp; Bugs\' and complete the template. We will respond as soon as we can.</string>
    <string name="invite_users">Invite Users</string>
    <string name="users_email">User\'s Email</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="delete_league">Delete League</string>
    <string name="delete_league_confirmation">Are you sure you want to delete</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="points">Pts</string>
    <string name="win_percentage">Win%</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_title">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_content">
        ScoreProf respects your privacy. Muntjac Solutions is the Data Controller for this Service. \n\n
        <b>1. Legal Basis (GDPR):</b> Our primary legal basis for processing your data (email address) is the <b>Performance of a Contract</b>. This data is necessary to provide your account and gaming features. We also rely on <b>Legitimate Interests</b> for security and <b>Consent</b> for personalized advertisements (handled via our consent provider). \n\n
        <b>2. Data Controller:</b> Muntjac Solutions, 9 rue de Condé, Bureau 3, 33000 Bordeaux, France. SIRET: 104 419 619 00010. Registered with the RNE. \n\n
        <b>3. Data Protection Contact:</b> In accordance with Art. 37 of the GDPR, our point of contact for privacy inquiries is <b>support@muntjac-solutions.com</b>. \n\n
        <b>4. Data Retention:</b> We retain your data according to French law: \n
        • <b>Account &amp; Contact:</b> 3 years after account closure or last active contact. \n
        • <b>Invitations:</b> Emails used for invites are deleted if not accepted within 30 days. \n
        • <b>Accounting Records:</b> 10 years as required by the French Commercial Code. \n
        • <b>Cookies/Analytics:</b> Maximum 13 months. \n\n
        <b>5. International Transfers:</b> Data is primarily hosted in London, UK (DigitalOcean Limited) and Stockholm, Sweden (AWS EMEA SARL). The UK has an <b>adequacy decision</b> from the European Commission. Sweden is part of the EEA. \n\n
        <b>6. Your Rights:</b> You have the right to access, rectify, or request erasure. Contact us or the CNIL. \n\n
        <b>7. Policy Changes:</b> Material changes will be notified via our News section. \n\n
        <b>8. Full Policy:</b> https://www.muntjac-solutions.com/privacy
    </string>
    <string name="copyright">Copyright © 2026 ScoreProf</string>
    <string name="email_validation_text">Please enter a valid email address</string>
    <string name="invite_subject">%1$s invited you to join league \'%2$s\'</string>
    <string name="invite_message">Hi!\n\n%1$s has invited you to join the league \'%2$s\' on the ScoreProf app.\n\nTo accept this invitation and start playing, open the ScoreProf app and select the league via Setup > Leagues.\n\nIf you don\'t have the app yet, you can download it here: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=cloud.scoreprof.app\n\nHappy playing!\nThe ScoreProf Team</string>
    <string name="legal_notice_title">Legal Notice</string>
    <string name="legal_notice_content">
        In accordance with the provisions of Articles 6-III and 19 of Law No. 2004-575 of June 21, 2004 for Confidence in the Digital Economy (LCEN), users of ScoreProf are informed of these legal notices.\n\n
        <b>Publisher:</b> Muntjac Solutions\n
        <b>Publication Director:</b> Mark Howell, Founder\n
        <b>Status:</b> Sole Proprietor (Unregulated Professional Practice)\n
        <b>SIRET:</b> 104 419 619 00010\n
        <b>Registration:</b> Registered with the National Business Registry (RNE)\n
        <b>Headquarters:</b> 9 rue de Condé, Bureau 3, 33000 Bordeaux, France\n
        <b>Phone:</b> 07 87 27 59 08\n
        <b>Email:</b> contact@muntjac-solutions.com\n\n
        <b>Data Protection:</b> For data privacy inquiries, see our Privacy Policy or contact support@muntjac-solutions.com.\n\n
        <b>Hosting:</b> This application is hosted by:\n\n
        <b>Digital Ocean Limited</b>\n
        Suite 7 Savant House, 63-65 Camden High Street, London NW1 7JL, United Kingdom\n
        Contact: https://www.digitalocean.com/company/contact/support\n\n
        <b>Amazon Web Services Emea Sarl, Sverige Filial</b>\n
        Malmskillnadsgatan 36, 111 57 Stockholm, Sweden\n
        Contact: https://aws.amazon.com/fr/contact-us/?nc1=f_m
    </string>
</resources>